ACWA Education Department Records 5619/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Brazil Labor Movement, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  Includes mostly Portuguese language material
- Brazil - Labor Movements, 1989-1993 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  Includes some Portuguese language material
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (Brussels, Belgium), 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions/International Trade Secretariats - International Labor Education Projects, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes news clipping
- Canada and NAFTA, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Canada Labor Movement, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1987-1992 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Central America (General), 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Costa Rico Labor/Popular Organizations, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Chile, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Cuba Labor Tour, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Dominican Republic Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  Includes two clothing tags; includes some Spanish language material
- Dominican Republic Seminar, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  March 26 - April 6, 1993; includes some Spanish language material; includes news paper
- Dominican Republic: General Information/Update, 1989-1993 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Dominican Republic Spanish Materials, 1988-1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Dominican Republic Articles, 1980-1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Dominican Republic Handwritten Notes, 1989-1993 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- F.A.T. (Frente Autentico del Trabajo), 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- FITTVCC/ORI, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  Includes several color photographs; includes some Spanish language material; includes newspaper
- Jose Ramirez (Biography), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- FITTVCC/ORI II, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Guatemala Labor Movement, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Guatemala Labor Movement Seminar, 1989-1993 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  March 8-9, 1993; includes some Spanish language material; includes a news clipping
- PRD - Congreso Nacional, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  Almost entirely Spanish language material
- El Salvador Labor Movement, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- El Salvador Social/Political Issues, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Venezuela Labor Unions, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  Includes some Spanish language material; includes newspaper
- Venezuela - Political Parties, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Workers Rights in Central America, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Travel Arrangements (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Background Information (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1979-1992 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  Includes Spanish language and English/Spanish material; includes newspaper
- Press (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- New York (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Texas (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Washington, D.C. (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Chicago (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Miami (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1992 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Ramirez Tour, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Correspondence (Jose Ramirez Tour), 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- FITTVCC/ORI, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1991 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1992 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- FITTVCC/ORI Summit on Regional Integration, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  Venezuela 1991; includes some Spanish language material
- FITTVCC/ORI Directory, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1990 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  Includes a color photograph on a postcard; includes some Spanish language material
- FITTVCC/ORI (up to 1989), 1973-1989 (Box 49, Folder 25)